just start with, you know, as you look
at everything, all the entire all the
activity you guys have done, you know,
across really the first few days, how
much more better do you feel about where
this roster is as you, you know, kind of
take the next step forward?
>> Feel great addressing the receiver room
and the O line room along with the
safety position. Uh, you know, I think
we're as we went into the draft, and I
think Andrew can speak to this more than
I can, but, uh,
it's where we hoped we would head, uh,
where we would address.
>> See him as a tackle to start obviously
has some flex we think could move
inside.
>> Talk about, you know, backto back
receivers in the first and second round.
That's doesn't happen often. So, what is
your reaction to getting those two guys?
>> Well, I think he compliments. Uh, if you
take Denzel after KC, I think he
compliments KC. He's a different body
type than what we have. Uh, we were
looking at uh
someone we thought could be a size
matchup and especially in the red zone,
which we did not have. So, loved his
competitive spirit. Uh, just talking
about Denzel now. spoke with Jed Fish,
his head coach at Washington, who I've
got a ton of respect for, been in the
NFL and and raved about Denzel,
loves to practice, competitive, a lot of
fight in him, he's come a long way as a
player and uh is only going to continue
to get better and we certainly needed to
to just continue to upgrade that
position and we did.
>> Coming out, you know, I know you guys
gave this house
But like to come out of this draft four
players in the first two nights that a
lot of folks had first round grades on.
>> Well, I mean ultimately now whether we
take them in the first round, second
round, third round, whatever their
grades are now, it's up to us as a
coaching staff to develop them. And
that's why we're hired. That's why
coaches are hired as to uh develop the
players that show up in your locker
room. And uh you know, you're always
trying to maximize a player's measurable
skill set and that's what we're that's
what we're going to fight like hell to
do.
>> Still kind of a middle offensive line. I
know there
has been about position.
>> There has been. And um there's a
possibility we'll still address that as
we get further into the draft.
>> Everybody's tired. I get it. I'm tired,
too.
>> Denzel's red zone ability. How important
was it to have two receivers that have,
I guess, complimentary skill sets to do
what you want to do offense?
>> Probably more important than usual just
to the makeup of our receiver room as it
sits right now. Would not have been as
big a deal um if you would have had some
bigger body types. But you when you look
at some of the body types we have when
we take the field every day, we
certainly needed to um certainly get
bigger. We certainly needed to add um
some size to that room and uh you know
Denzel provided that for us.
>> Question for Andrew, but kind of unusual
to trade out of the room and then come
back in.
>> It was a lot of fun.
>> I mean, it was a heck of a ride. I was
just in there for the ride, so it was
pretty cool.
>> After all,
>> you're talking about are you talking
about Barber?
>> Yeah.
>> No, I mean, we really liked him from the
jump. Um, you don't know how the board
again Andrew can answer this. You don't
know in my limited experience of of
this, you don't know how it's going to
go. There's certain players that are
picked higher than you would have
thought and there's others that are a
little bit lower. Certainly, we knew we
had to address uh the offensive line.
And so, you know, as it as as he was
still up on the board, I think the
opportunity to move back and then as it
as it continued, then let's not wait any
longer. Let's go up and get him. And uh
we're fired up to get him.
>> The competition now in the receiver
room, what do you see? in total there.
>> Well, I just think you have to keep
adding to the room as best you can. Um,
you're trying to raise the floor. I
mean, ultimately in any position group,
you start by raising the floor and
developing who you have. And that
started this past week. So, it just
turned out the way the draft unfolded.
And Andrew again can speak to this that
when we got to, you know, the spot that
we had at seven would be actually 39,
but today seven, uh, we did have
opportunities and they'll speak to it to
move back, but we really thought at that
pick, take Denzel. Do
>> you feel with the guys that you added,
the guys, Daryl, do you feel pretty good
about the potential explosiveness of
your offense?
>> I feel better.
You mentioned safety being something you
guys are obviously looking at in the
other side of things. Just what what
strikes you and stands out about Emanuel
McNeil Warren and what do you like with
with what he brings to the table?
>> Um length, speed, tough.
That's it. I mean he's got great length,
excellent speed, and he'll hit the heck
out of you. I mean, that's three pretty
good characteristics of a safety.
>> Just yesterday, so last day, were you
kind of surprised at how the board fell
today?
>> Uh, surprised. I I would not say that. I
I would not say that
of of picks.
I would not say uh that I was surprised,
especially on the offensive guys. If you
asked me where those picks went,
I would have said, you know, pretty
close to where we kind of had targeted,
where we thought they would be
available. Again, Andrew can speak to
that. I'm speaking for me, you know, in
terms of where I would have thought uh
because I did evaluate all those players
and I would have said that was about
right and the board actually played out
that way. How much more fun is it doing
this if fun's the right word doing this
as a head coach instead of offensive
coordinator?
>> Well, I have one more level of uh input
I guess as opposed to a step down, you
know, from the head coach and the OC.
But
um ultimately it's more fun because um
you know when you're an offensive
coordinator you're really not
responsible for winning. You're
responsible for scoring and when you're
the head coach we're responsible for
winning. So I certainly want to score
but uh more importantly we got to win
football games. And so when it came down
to you know when you're talking about
defensive players I'm all for great
defensive players going to help us win.
Ultimately, that's our job as an
organization, a head coach, is to do
everything in our power uh to put a
roster together that gives us a chance
to compete every week and ultimately uh
turn this organization into a consistent
winning one.
>> Mentioned how your messaging about what
type of players you want is really
direct. They get the idea of what you're
looking for. Do you feel like you've
been listened to is this is the type of
player I want to do? I want to run my
offense.
>> Not really. I mean, it it doesn't really
work that way. It really there are
pieces like that. I I take that back. I
there are elements of what you may need
from a
position, what type of tight end, for
instance. Do you want a fullback? You're
going to be an 11 personnel team. So
personnel-wise, much more than maybe the
player, because I don't think the
the parts that make a player, how
they're wired, their toughness, mental
toughness,
you know, their self-awareness, do they
love to practice, do they love football?
I think that's from the jump, that's who
you want to surround yourself with. So,
but maybe a little bit in terms of how
you see usage of a player. It does you
no good to take a player without a plan
for them. And I think we all saw KC the
same way, how we could utilize him. I
think we all saw the same way in terms
of Denzel.
I think you know when you talk offensive
line, you're just trying some guys think
um can play tackle but also have
position flex. I think that's the best
way to go about it.
>> Speaking of fullbacks, do you and your
staff still consider Cington I was
fullback.
>> Well, it's funny. The first time I saw
him, I'm like, "You're the fullback
here, right?" You know, and he looked at
me like, you know, "No, I'm a defensive
tackle." So, that didn't go over great.
The first conversation I had with him,
I'm joking. He was he was fine. But
ultimately, you know, he's going to want
to play defensive first. but he
certainly um showed some promise in the
back field and obvious
toughness and the want to and you can
see that on special teams. He played on
specials. You could see him on kickoff.
So, I do think that is an option as we
move forward. But again, I think
depending on how much you're going to
use that position, which we'll as we go
along, we'll find out. It's hard if
you're going to be a 21 personnel team
to have a part-time fullback. So, you're
we're gonna have to make that decision.
Is it is it situationally is it
situation only, you know, where you're
only talking about a little piece, maybe
goal line, short yardage, or is it more
than that as a normal rundown piece? And
if it is, then we're going to need more
than a part-time fullback.
>> Go ahead.
>> We didn't get to watch the practices of
mini camp just the first one obviously.
Um so can I mean can you kind of share
how how did Deshawn and and Shador and
Dylan look now you got
>> we just couldn't get past the draft and
get right on to to back to the
quarterback. Anybody got some Miles
questions too while we're at it? I mean
hell. Um while we're just you know here
at night. Um first off I'll address the
question. First of all it was awesome
three days. The weather was unbelievable
to get out on the grass and pump the
music and get fired up being together
and the neighbors complained and we
didn't care and we pumped up the music
louder. they don't like it, they can
move. And so I didn't care. And it was
like, you know, being out there with the
guys and just getting a little bit of a
feel for who we have uh on our roster.
And I thought all three quarterbacks at
times you could see,
you know, the positives in their game
and learning the new system and they've
been awesome in the meeting rooms and
and on the field and uh it was just kind
of dipping our toe in the water, but I
thought, you know, Deshawn looked really
good at times and there's other things
you got to work on. Same with Shidor and
uh with Dylan. So, I didn't really
really didn't do a deep dive into all of
them, but it was a heck of a lot of fun
being out there. I can tell you that.
>> Upstairs sitting next to Andrew on the
road. Um, you know, you know, what's
that been like for you as a head coach?
And, uh, you and Andrew, you know, find
yourselves thinking alike as as the
board comes together, as you're sitting
next to each other. Well,
I think we see
players the same way in their value, how
they're wired. That part of it is for
sure.
Other than that, I just have a small
like
picture of each player. I certainly
don't have the picture of every single
player that they do that they've spent
years at least one year and probably
more than that on a player. So, what I
do know is the players that I did look
at and I listen to the scouts and we all
talk about how they're wired and do we
want them representing the Cleveland
Browns? Is that who we want? And we've
got a great group. We're just
continually trying to raise the floor,
but I've been
thoroughly impressed with the process of
Andrew and his staff, and I can see how
the picks came to fruition last year,
with the talent that we have, and I I
feel really good about what we're adding
at this point.
>> When it comes to Rudy want to play a
bunch of three safety,
>> I'm not really going to get into what
we're going to do. um considering we
won't have film yet for our first game.
So, we're just fired up to have him.
>> Go back to the receivers. I know when
you first talked about your offense and
this offenses identity, talked about
scoring being the most paramount thing.
Like, do you feel good about the
different ways those guys added so far?
>> I do. Um again, like I said, I think
they complement each other. I think it
started with we had to address the
offensive line. I mean, that's
in both areas. That's, you know, the
receiver position and and the offensive
line. And I really feel good about, you
know, where we're at at this point.
>> Good. Last one.
>> And that is, uh, you know, in getting
your evaluation of how the quarterbacks
looked.
There are still plenty left on the board
on the final day of the draft. Do you
Andrew has talked about it's wholly
realistic. You guys could add another
back to the room. Would you be
kind of excited to do that. And do you
see are there some guys that you like
from the quarterback position?
>> We'll see how it plays out. I don't
think there's any position
that is off the board that we wouldn't
take even after taking two receivers. I
we might have taken a third. We might
take another offensive lineman. Um could
be a quarterback. I don't think there's
any position when I left the um
you know the draft room that that I
didn't see anything that wouldn't you
know that wouldn't interest us at any
position.
>> Thank you.
>> All right.
>> Yep.